selectminds.com 2012-10-01

# Privacy Policy

EFFECTIVE April 30, 2012

### Introduction

SelectMinds adheres to the US-EU Safe Harbor privacy principles.

SelectMinds collects and stores personally identifiable information on behalf of clients. This information, as well as critical company assets, is stored on the SelectMinds computer network. Access to any personally identifiable information will be limited only to employees that require access to that data in order to perform their jobs. 

### Definitions 

“Members”: client approved employee and alumni participants who utilize SelectMind's social network applications and provide Personally Identifiable Information.

“Personally Identifiable Information”/“Information”: any piece of information which can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person.

“Principles”: the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles.

“Sensitive Personal Information”: means personal information that reveals race, ethnic origin, sexual orientation, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or that concerns an individual's health.

“Users”: employees, contractors, consultants, temporaries, and other workers at SelectMinds.

### Privacy Policy

SelectMinds believes in protecting our clients and client member's privacy.  When we collect Personally Identifiable Information via our software application, we follow the privacy principles of the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Agreement concerning the transfer of personal data from the European Union to the United States of America.  Accordingly, we follow the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles published by the U.S Department of Commerce. 

SelectMinds does NOT collect "Sensitive Personal Information."

### PRINCIPLES 

### Notice 

_Notification of changes to this policy will be communicated to all Users. This policy is available to all Users and will be posted in a manner that all Users have access. SelectMinds expects Users to comply with the letter and the spirit of this agreement. If there are questions concerning any privacy concerns please contact  David Pollack. At no point will Users access and / or use this data for any purpose other than in execution of their job responsibilities. SelectMinds recognizes that the nature of our services and products dictate that Personally Identifiable Information is received from our clients and client Members. Only staff Users who require access to sensitive data in order to perform their jobs will be granted access. This access will be controlled by appointed SelectMinds management and will be controlled employing all security SOPs as outlined in Physical Security and Logical Security SOPs._

Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language to client Members, when asked via our software applications to provide Personally Identifiable Information, of the purpose for which we collect and use such information. SelectMinds does not sell or otherwise make available any Information received from its clients. Additionally, SelectMinds does not share Information from any client with a third party unless agreed to in writing by all parties or required by law, and if so shared, shared Members will receive notice of the types of third parties who receive this information and the choices available to them to limit the use and disclosure of this Information.  Information will be provided to all Members as to how they can contact SelectMinds with any inquiries or complaints.

### Choice 

SelectMind's will ensure that Members are given a choice to choose (opt out) in any potential circumstance where their Personally Identifiable Information is to be disclosed to a third party or used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected and authorized by the Member.  

### Onward Transfer 

In the event that SelectMinds will disclose Personally Identifiable Information to a third party, the company shall apply the Notice and Choice principles herein and notify the individual Member of such disclosure and allow the Member the choice to opt out of such disclosure.  SelectMinds will ensure that any third party for which Information may disclosed subscribes to the same level of privacy protection as is required by these Principles.

### Data Security 

SelectMinds will maintain reasonable precautionary policies and procedures to ensure the protection of Information collected from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  Company has in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Information.  SelectMinds cannot guarantee the security of Information on or transmitted via the Internet. 

### Data Integrity 

SelectMinds will only process Personally Identifiable Information for the purpose of facilitating Member social networking relationships and as authorized by the Member, and will not use or process this Information in any other way.  To the extent necessary for these purposes, SelectMinds will take reasonable steps to ensure that the Information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. 

### Access 

SelectMinds shall allow Members access to their Personally Identifiable Information and allow the Member to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information, as required by law.

### Enforcement 

SelectMinds uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this Privacy Policy and will periodically verify that the Policy is accurate and comprehensive for the Information collected, that the Policy will be prominently displayed, and that the Policy will be completely implemented in conformity with the Principles.  We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Principles, and if a complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through our internal process, we agree to dispute resolution using the Better Business Bureau EU Safe Harbor Program.

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, SelectMinds commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact SelectMinds at:

SelectMinds Inc.  
149 5th Avenue  
New York, NY 10010  
Attn: Chief Financial Officer  

SelectMinds has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by SelectMinds, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

SelectMinds recognizes the right for each client to dictate their own privacy policy which governs the relationship between their organization and the end users/Members. SelectMinds will ensure all services provided conform to clients' privacy policies, at a minimum such policies will adhere to the Principles herein.
